http://www.imextechnical.co.uk/privacy/

color#666666http://www.imextechnical.co.uk/wp-content/themes/zap-installable/http://www.imextechnical.co.uk/#ef8c25style2
Swindon, Wiltshire
Client Support
Telephone 01793 781800
PrivacyPrivacy Policy and GDPR General StatementIMEX Technical Services Ltd is committed to European General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) compliance, which comes into force on the 25th May, 2018 and applies this when dealing with all data received from visitors to the site.IMEX Technical Services Ltd has taken many steps to protect the personal data of our customers, including but not limited to:IMEXs solutions are provided using established and industry-leading technology providers and  platforms. These providers have stated their commitment to compliance with GDPR.IMEXs cloud based offerings are localised in the region where our customer is located (UK or EU) unless the customer expressly designates another locality.IMEX maintains and administers a security policy with physical, technical, and administrative safeguards designed to protect the security, integrity and confidentiality of customer data.Controlling your personal informationIMEX will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we are required by law to do so.You may request details of personal information which IMEX hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998, if you would like a copy of the information held please write to   requesting this.If you have previously agreed to IMEX using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing IMEX at   or by using the unsubscribe link on the newsletter/service updates.IMEX only hold personal data for as long as necessary. Once data is no longer needed it is deleted.For administrative reasons email subscription data may be passed to and stored securely with third party service providers, although IMEX will never sell, rent or exchange mailing lists.In accordance with the Privacy and Electronic Communications (EC Directive) Regulations 2003, IMEX never send bulk unsolicited emails, (Spam) to email addresses.IMEX may send emails to existing customers or prospective customers who have made an enquiry with us, regarding products or services directly provided by IMEX and emails sent by IMEX will be clearly marked as originating from IMEX.Links to other websitesThe IMEX website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that IMEX do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, IMEX cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.Cookies used by IMEX Technical LtdIMEX use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.Our cookies do not contain or pass any personal, confidential or financial information or any other information that could be used to identify individual visitors.The tracking cookies that we use are for Google Analytics. These allow IMEX to count page visits and traffic sources, so IMEX can measure and improve the performance of the company website. The tracking cookies are anonymous and so don’t hold any private data about you. Nor can they be used to share information about you with third parties.What exactly is a Cookie?Cookie is technical term for a tiny text file left on your computer by websites you visit. Each cookie is accessible only by the website that created it, and is used to store useful information on how you use that particular site.If you know where to look, you’ll find hundreds, perhaps even thousands of cookies stored on your computer’s hard disk. Each one is unique, and relates to a specific website. Don’t panic, a cookie cannot contain viruses or malware and cannot install anything on your computer.Cookies are useful. When you do an online shop on an ecommerce site and it greets you by name, it’s because it detected the cookie stored on your computer from your last visit. Equally, when you click a “Like” button and your Facebook account automatically opens up showing your profile, Facebook cookies on your computer have allowed this to happen.Why we tell you about our cookiesIt’s the law. The Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations have been updated this year, stating that site users should be fully informed about the information being stored in cookies on websites they visit.What should you do?If you’re happy with the above then please continue to use IMEX Technical Services Ltd without changing your settings and IMEX will assume that you are happy to receive all cookies on the IMEX Technical Services Ltd website. However, if you would like to you can change your cookie settings at any time.To find out more about cookies, including how to see previous cookies have been set on your machine, and how to manage or delete them, please visit www.allaboutcookies.org.If you have any questions relating to our Privacy Policy please contact us via  Want to find out more?Leave your details and one of our representatives will give you a call. REQUEST A CALL BACKRequest a Call Back
Name * Telephone * Day Time
Please enter the characters shown in the image into the field below:
You are here: Home » Privacy Subscribe to the IMEX Newsletter Email Address *
Get in Touch IMEX Technical Services Ltd Delta 500, Welton Road Swindon Wiltshire SN5 7XE United Kindom Telephone: 01793 781800 Email: IT Solutions, Support & ConsultancyIT Consultancy for BusinessSME Outsourced IT PartnerIT Support and MonitoringIT Management for BusinessCloud ServicesHosted EmailEmail SecurityEmail ArchivingCloud BackupBusiness ContinuityRecent Posts 23rd Dec Christmas and New Year Opening Times 2019/20 23rd Dec Seasons greetings from all at IMEX 23rd Aug Microsoft Silver Partner re-qualification 5th Mar IMEX achieve Cyber Essentials Certification 25th Feb Microsoft Silver Partner re-qualification© 2020 IMEX Technical Services LtdPrivacySitemap Designed and Built by paged
